moxielinks.com 2017-12-01

# Moxielinks - Privacy Policy

**Privacy Policy**

At Moxie Links, we are committed to protecting your privacy. Any information we collect, such as email addresses, is submitted at the visitor’s will. We do not and will not share any personal information with any third parties. We have NO access to any information collected by our Payment Services Providers. 

**Cookies**

All browsers offer “cookies” and if you permit their use, they will store small amounts of data on your computer about your visit to the site that placed the cookie. A cookie is a small text file. It is not a program, or a plug-in. It could not be used as a virus, and it cannot access your hard drive. Cookies simply assist in tracking which features you like the most and allow content to be customized upon your return, according to prior preferences at that site. They would not gather or hold any personal information. 

Moxie Links collects data about your activities that does not personally or directly identify you when you visit our website, the website of entities for which we serve advertisements (our “Advertisers”), or the websites and online services where we display advertisements (“Publishers”). This information may include the content you view, the date and time that you view this content, the products you purchase, or your location information associated with your IP address. We use the information we collect to serve you more relevant advertisements. 

**Moxie Links will NOT:**

  * Use cookies to identify, monitor or track any personally identifiable information.

  * Have cookies that contain any personally identifiable information about you.

  * Merge or associate our cookie information with any other visitor’s confidential and identifiable data obtained by us or from 3rd parties. You also have flexible choices in respect to cookies. By simply modifying your browser preferences, you have the right to choose whether to accept all cookies, to be notified when a cookie is set or to reject all cookies.

However, please note that if you reject some or all cookies, your experience at our sites and on other sites throughout the web may not be complete. Some sites require cookies to function, such as those with e-commerce features. In addition, if you disable cookies, you will not be eligible to take advantage of personalized content delivery offered by us or other Internet sites.
